A Guide to the Pocahontas Mines Collection, 1883-1997
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Unscanned rolls, 1883-1997, 360 Cubic Feet; 463 boxes
  - Miscellaneous Documents (Box 646)
    - [Document] "Annual Shipments From Pocahontas Field", 1951 (Box 646)
      Tabulated data for coal production data from all producers of coal in the Pocahontas coal field from 1913 to 1952.
    - [Document] "Annual Shipments From Pocahontas Field", 1955 (Box 646)
    - [Document] Coal Assay reporting sheet. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1948/02/26 (Box 646)
    - [Document] Pulaski Lease-Coal Section along outcrop stripping on Low Gap Fork of Dan's Br, 1949/11/14 (Box 646)
    - Proposed Stores Building, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Pocahontas, Virginia, 1955/05/11 (Box 646)
    - [Document] "2 1/2% Ash in all Sizes..How Imperial Smokeless Does it" publication from Coal Age, 1961/05 (Box 646)
    - [Document] Report and Supplemental Report on the Boone County Coal Corporation by Walter Gillman & Edward V. D'Invilliers, Geologists and Mining Engineers, 1917, 1919 (Box 646)
    - [Document] "Index - Itmann Const. Maps, undated (Box 646)
      Detailed index and listing of all maps from Itmann by job number.
    - [Document] Engineer's notes and calculations on haul road grades, undated (Box 646)
    - [Document] "Pocahontas #6 Seam on Unleased lands of the Pocahontas Coal and Coke Co., in Wyoming County, West Virginia.", undated (Box 646)
    - [Document] "Report on No. 3 Seam on Unleased Lands of the Pocahontas Coal and Coke Co., on Guyan River in and around Mullins, West Virginia, on the Guyandotte River. ", undated (Box 646)
    - [Document] Correlation of Coal Beds in Eastern Kentucky, West Virginia and Virginia table, undated (Box 646)
      Table showing the alternative names given to the same coal bed in different areas.
    - [Document] Inter-office communication note of Lake Coal Division of Consolidation Coal Company Inc. about Union Carbide Metals Div. Mine No. 3 coal assay results. (Box 646)
    - [Document] unlabelled orange 3 inch floppy disk- content unknown. (Box 646)
    - [Document] Engineer's calculations for length and slope for conveyors. (Box 646)
    - [Document] Manila Envelope return addressed to Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., Mining Department, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Box 646)
    - [Document] Power Consumption Charts. 10 pages. (Box 646)
  - Photographs and Mounted Photographs (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Tipple and Head House of Jacobs Fork mine. Pocahontas Coal Company. Squire, McDowell County, West Virginia, 1940/04/10 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] East View of Tipple of Jacobs Fork mine. Pocahontas Coal Company. Squire, McDowell County, West Virginia, 1940/04/10 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Norfolk and Western Railroad Car full of 6" Lump Coal at Jacobs Fork mine. Pocahontas Coal Company. Squire, McDowell County, West Virginia, 1940/04/10 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] 1-1/4" x 3" Stove Coal pile close-up. Jacobs Fork mine. Pocahontas Coal Company. Squire, McDowell County, West Virginia, 1940/04/10 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] 3"x 6" Egg Coal close-up. Jacobs Fork mine. Pocahontas Coal Company. Squire, McDowell County, West Virginia, 1940/04/10 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] 6" Lump Coal close-up. Jacobs Fork mine. Pocahontas Coal Company. Squire, McDowell County, West Virginia, 1940/04/10 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Profile shot of Bolt Mining Co. Tipple. Bolt Mining Company, Bolt, Wyoming County, West Virginia, Slab Fork District, 1959/03 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] "8" x 3-1/2" washed egg; possibly Pocahontas coal, very soft." Bolt Mining Company, Bolt, Wyoming County, West Virginia., Slab Fork District, 1959/03 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] "Another car of 8" x 3-1/2" washed egg coal; coal in this car was firmer than the one shown in other picture. Egg shows slight orange stain from strip mine. " Bolt Mining Company, Bolt, Wyoming County, West Virginia., Slab Fork District, 1959/03 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] No. 3 Tipple of Union Carbide Metals. S.P. Hightop, Kanawha County, West Virginia, 1964/07 (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Ralph Cox - Prep Plant Engineer squats atop a railroad car full of cleaned coal, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] View of Tipple and rail cars being loaded with coal. Princess Dorothy Coal Co. Robin Hood, West Virginia, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] No. 5 Block Seam outcrop with two miners in foreground. Princess Dorothy Coal Co. Robin Hood Mine, West Virginia, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph]Myers Whaley Loading Machine and Miners Loading Strip Coal from the Middle Bench. Princess Dorothy Coal Co. Robin Hood Mine, West Virginia, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Bulldozer pushing Coal to Myers Whaley Loading Machine for Loading as Miners watch. Princess Dorothy Coal Co. Robin Hood Mine, West Virginia, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Foremen Supervising loading of tram cars on middle bench. Princess Dorothy Coal Co. Robin Hood Mine, West Virginia, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Bulldozers Removing the Shale parting from the Top of the Bottom Bench of the Seam. Princess Dorothy Coal Co. Robin Hood Mine, West Virginia, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] "View of Golden Ridge No. 6 tipple of the Minds Coal mining Corporation, on the Elk River side of Point Mountain." The Minds coal Mining Corporation--No. 5, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] View of a pile of Golden Ridge coal lumps with Superintendent J. W. Close standing in the foreground. The Minds coal Mining Corporation--No. 5, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] View of Golden Ride No.6 Mine Entrance/Portal and Mine Office. The Minds coal Mining Corporation--No. 5, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] View of working face and roof supports of an unidentified coal mine, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Two miners work to lift a lump of coal into a tram car in an unidentified coal mine, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] View from inside a railroad car half full of 4" egg and 6" block coal, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] View from inside a railroad car half full of2-1/2" x 4" egg coal, undated (Box 646)
    - [Photograph] Photo showing minder testing roof in unidentified mine working in Upper Mercer Seam. (Box 646)
      Caption says "Sandstone cover UPPER MERCER SEAM. 8 Feet and one inch (all coal). Opening on Alkire and & Perrine Farm. 1/4th mile north of Laurel Branch of Little Kanawha River.
  - Small Miscellaneous Documents (Box 646)
    - State and Local Tax Levies sheet-1943 for Town of Pocahontas, Tazewell County, Virginia, 1943 (Box 646)
    - C.B. Hancock - Broker, Telegram to Mr William J. Skewes notifying his client of the purchase of 5 shares of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Common stock. (Box 646)
    - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Inc - Common Stock Dividend card (Box 646)
    - [Document] Vornado Air Circulator user manual, undated (Box 646)
    - [Document] 3" x 5" section of topographic map of Rolfe Mine property with hand-drawn coalbed elevation contour lines (Box 646)
    - [Document] 4" x 6" blank mining department memo slip. Sketch and engineer's notes on an electric motor located on the back. (Box 646)
  - Miscellaneous Documents (Box 646)
    - [Document] Technical Publication No. 441, Class F, Coal Division, No. 50. "The Low-volatile Coal Field of Southern West Virginia" by Howard Eavenson, 1931 (Box 646)
    - Coal Field Correlation Sheet, The M. A. Hanna Company, Cleveland, By P.E. Gallagher, 1940 (Box 646)
    - The Pennsylvania Railroad Regional Map, 1955/11 (Box 646)
    - Map Showing Lines of Railroad Companies and Territory Involved, 1962/10/01 (Box 646)
    - Map of Norfolk and Western Railroad system, 1965/05 (Box 646)
    - Table VII - Correlation of Coal Beds in Eastern Kentucky, West Virginia, and Virginia, undated (Box 646)
    - Chart Showing Stratigraphic Position of Coal Beds in the Southwest Virginia Field, United States Geological Survey. (Box 646)
    - [Document] Drainage Tunnel of the Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Box 646)
    - Personnel Records file "Engineering Employment: Clinchfield Coal Corporation" (Box 646)
      RESTRICTED ACCESS: Personnel Records
  - Alder F. Castanoli Consulting Mining Engineer (Box 647)
    - Coal cleaning and processing facilities designs for Crane Creek Mine by Alder F. Castanoli Consulting Mining Engineer (4 sheets) (Box 647)
  - Enterprise Wheel and Car Corp. (Box 647)
    - Typical coal blending and coal slurry processing facilities designed for Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. by Enterprise Wheel & Car Corp. (11 sheets) (Box 647)
  - Heyl & Patterson, Inc. (Box 647)
    - Convoy system Drawings and proposed plans for upgrades to Itmann Prep Plant by Heyl & Patterson, Inc. (26 Sheets) (Box 647)
  - J.O. Lively Manufacturing & Equipment Corp. (Box 647)
    - Keeper Mine raw coal handling and clean coal storage facilities designed by J.O. Lively Manufacturing & Equipment Corp. (7 sheets) (Box 647)
  - Link-Belt Company (Box 647)
    - Itmann Coal Company Coal Preparation Plant Plans drawn by the Link-Belt Company (50 Sheets), 1948-1950 (Box 647)
      There are images on VT ImageBase of this prep plant.
  - Miscellaneous Maps and Drawings (Box 647)
    - Surge and Blending Facilities at Itmann Prep plant. designed by Valley Steel Corporation (2 sheets) (Box 647)
    - Wall Reinforcing for Itmann Mine, drawn William L. Clark, Jr. Consulting Engineer (Box 647)
    - General Highway map of McDowell County, West Virginia (Box 647)
    - Cyclone Support for McComas Plant designed by West Virginia Steel Corp. (Box 647)
    - 36" Belt conveyor assembly details by Persingers Inc., Machinery Division (2 copies) (Box 647)
  - Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Box 647)
    - Rolfe Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Vivian Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Goodwill Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Elkhorn Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Pocahontas No. 1 Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Boissevain Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Ashland, Upper Northfork Hollow, Cherokee Refuse Pile, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Peerless Mine Refuse Piles No. 2 & 3 map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Jenkin Jones Mine Refuse Piles map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Berwind Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Crane Creek Mine Refuse Pile map, 1974 (Box 647)
    - Surge and Blending Facilities technical drawing, Itmann Mine, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (10 sheets) (Box 647)
    - Detailed plan and profile drawings of Kepler Mine coal storage and loading facilities (4 sheets) (Box 647)
  - The Daniels Company (Box 647)
    - Coal Processing system diagrams and plans by The Daniels Company (14 sheets) (Box 647)
  - Deerfield (Box 648)
    - Deerfield Mine - Pump Hole Plan and Section of Mine Area Relative to Proposed Sump. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1956/02/02 (Box 648)
    - Deerfield Mine: Tipple Water Supply. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1956/08/08 (Box 648)
    - Deerfield Mine Proposed Slurry Disposal. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1956/11/29 (Box 648)
    - Deerfield Mine Proposed Slurry Disposal. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (copy), 1956/11/29 (Box 648)
    - Air Shaft Locations and Cross Sections. Deerfield Mine. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1957/05/07 (Box 648)
    - Deerfield Tipple Flow Diagram Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 648)
  - Itmann (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 648)
    - Itmann Tipple and Preparation Plant and other surface facilities technical drawings (61 sheets) (Box 648)
  - Itmann (Folder 2 of 5) (Box 648)
    - Proposed Projection of Itmann Mine workings in No. 3 seam. Itmann leasehold, Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/07 (Box 648)
    - Proposed Projection map of mining on No. 3 Seam on the Itmann leasehold, 1947/04/15 (Box 648)
    - Section thru tipple head house and center line of raw coal Gallery - Longbranch location, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (4 sheets), 1947/06/06 (Box 648)
    - Proposed Mine Projection map, Itmann Mine, Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/06/15 (Box 648)
    - Estimate on building repairs, Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/06/27 (Box 648)
    - Coal Sections from Mine workings map on Itmann Leasehold, 1947/07/03 (Box 648)
    - Refuse track layout, alignment and grades map. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1949/02/02 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Store proposed floor plan. Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1949/03/02 (Box 648)
    - Long Branch Portal - Itmann, West Virginia, 1949/08/24 (Box 648)
    - Layout of Buildings & Facilities at Long Branch Driftsmouth. Itmann, West Virginia, 1950/09/05 (Box 648)
    - Slack Coal storage map, Itmann mine, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1955/02/17 (Box 648)
    - Map showing Railway Net west of Glenlyn which serves Boissevain, Crane Creek, JenkinJones and Rolfe Mines, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1956/09/11 (Box 648)
    - Plan & Detail: Single Compartment Intake Air Shaft. Itmann Mines, 1958/05/19 (Box 648)
    - Itmann No. 2 Mine map, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1959/02/24 (Box 648)
    - Proposed Projection of Itmann Mine workings in No. 3 seam. Itmann leasehold, Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Time and Prep Plant time studies (5 sheets) (Box 648)
    - Proposed temporary Coal Cleaning and Loading Facilities for Preparation and Loading during Construction Period. (Box 648)
    - Proposed Basin for storage of tipple slurry water & final settling of solids drawing. (Box 648)
  - Itmann (Folder 3 of 5) (Box 648)
    - Diagrammatic Sketch and Flow Chart of Proposed Tipple, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Itmann, West Virginia, 1947/05/27 (Box 648)
    - Profile Proposed Tipple Layout at Long Branch, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/06/02 (Box 648)
    - Additional Area Required for Refuse Disposal, Itmann Mine, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/06/24 (Box 648)
    - Railroad Tipple Track Layout and Virginian Main Line Proposed Revision, I-5-2, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/07/02 (Box 648)
    - Railroad Tipple Track Layout and Virginian Main Line Proposed Revision, I-5-1, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/07/02 (Box 648)
    - Proposed Complete Plant layout at Itmann. I-2-4, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/07/02 (Box 648)
    - Plan of Tipple and Track Location to include Location and Profile of Road. Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1948/02/16 (Box 648)
    - House Layout. Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1948/02/21 (Box 648)
    - Plant & Track Layout. Itmann Mine. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1948/06/03 (Box 648)
    - Mine Track Layout Alignment and Grades, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1948/12/23 (Box 648)
    - Map Showing Layout of Proposed Septic Tanks to be Built at Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1950/01/12 (Box 648)
    - Initial Layout for Long Branch Mine (Surface structures, Portals, Fan Intake). Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1950/02/01 (Box 648)
    - Sketch Showing location of Cross Sections For Proposed Dirty Water Settling Pond Below Long Branch, 1950/03/01 (Box 648)
    - Map showing proposed slurry ponds and slack coal storage. Itmann tipple, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1955/02/17 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Slack coal storage sheet no 2, 1955/02/17 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Slack Coal Storage sheet 1. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1955/02/17 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine: Proposed Slurry Disposal plan and map. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1956/11/29 (Box 648)
    - Proposed Slurry Disposal, Itmann Mine, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1956/11/29 (Box 648)
    - Map of Elevations at Itmann Mine along Guyandotte River. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Division of Consolidation Coal Co.), 1959/08/11 (Box 648)
    - Untitled map of surface structures of unknown location, undated (Box 648)
    - Flowsheet for Itmann Mine, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 648)
    - Itmann Colliery Tram Road: Topography from Itmann, No. 18 to Still Run and Guyandotte Side Sheet 1 of 3, undated (Box 648)
    - Itmann Colliery Tram Road: Topography from Itmann, No. 18 to Still Run and Guyandotte Side Sheet 2 of 3, undated (Box 648)
    - Itmann Colliery Tram Road: Topography from Itmann, No. 18 to Still Run and Guyandotte Side Sheet 3 of 3, undated (Box 648)
    - Map of Guyandotte Mains, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Division of Consolidation Coal Co.), undated (Box 648)
    - Untitled drawing. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Division of Consolidation Coal Co.), undated (Box 648)
    - Untitled map of Beech Fork Branch (Box 648)
    - Blank drawing sheet with Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (Division of Consolidation Coal Co.) Pocahontas, Virginia Engineering Office Title Block. (Box 648)
  - Itmann (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 648)
    - Proposed Complete Plant layout at Itmann. I-2-5, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/07/02 (Box 648)
    - Proposed Outside Mine Track Layout for Tipple location at Long Branch, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/10/22 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Tram Road from No. 18 drift to Guyandotte Bridge. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Sheet 3 of 5, 1958/04/17 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Tram Road from No. 18 drift to Guyandotte Bridge. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Sheet 4 of 5, 1958/04/17 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Tram Road from No. 18 drift to Guyandotte Bridge. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. Sheet 5 of 5, 1958/04/17 (Box 648)
    - Map of Old Slurry Pond and Cleaning Plant, Itmann Tipple, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1958/12/15 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Refuse Thickener, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1959/10/20 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine No. 3 Tie plan of Bridge Crossing River, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1960/08/01 (Box 648)
    - Itmann No. 3 Mine Cabin Creek Ventilation Shaft details, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1961/03/31 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Tipple Topography for Railroad car unloading Facilities. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1961/07/10 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine Refuse and Slurry Disposal Flow sheet and map, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1962/04/03 (Box 648)
    - Itmann Tipple elevation: Conveyor to Refuse Bin Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (4 sheets), undated (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine location of Slate dump and Proposed Refuse Belt, Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (8 sheets), undated (Box 648)
    - Itmann Tipple - Proposed Paving. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., undated (Box 648)
    - Itmann Mine No. 3 Cabin Creek ventilation plan near shaft. (Box 648)
  - Itmann (Folder 5 of 5) (Box 648)
    - Itmann Tipple technical drawings of Various parts and systems. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. (97 sheets), 1947-1958 (Box 648)
  - Miscellaneous Maps (Box 649)
    - Map of Pocahontas Coal Land Co. And Black Betsey Properties. Kanawha, West Virginia, 1918 (Box 649)
    - Map of land owned by Blue Jay Lumber Co. and others. Mercer County, West Virginia, 1936 (Box 649)
    - Property Map of Buchanan County, Virginia, 1946 (Box 649)
    - Leasehold of the Mill Creek Coal and Coke Co. Pocahontas Coal and Coke Company, 1925/03 (Box 649)
    - Map of Lands belonging to Lackawanna Coal and Lumber Co. in Boone Co. West Virginia, 1925/08/25 (Box 649)
    - Map of Mines serviced by Virginia Railway, Kanawha, Glen Jean & Eastern Railroad, Chesapeake & Ohio Railways, 1927/06/29 (Box 649)
    - Map of Tract No. 1. Coal, Coke & Byproducts Corporation, Malden Dist. Kanawha county, West Virginia, 1928/07/12 (Box 649)
    - Railroad route and Property map of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. land within the Pocahontas Coal Field, undated (Box 649)
    - Railroad route and Property map of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. land within the Pocahontas Coal Field, undated (Box 649)
    - Railroad route and Property map of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. land within the Pocahontas Coal Field, undated (Box 649)
    - Map Showing lands owned and leased by American Collieries Co. Snow Hill, West Virginia, undated (Box 649)
    - Map showing railroad routes and Elk River Coal & Lumber Company. Widen, West Virginia, undated (Box 649)
    - Map of property lines of Nicklett Coal Company and proposed entries into coal seam along Kanawha River, undated (Box 649)
    - Map of Coal lands: Piney Coking Coal Land Company, McCreery Central Pocahontas Coal Land Company, James T. McCreery Company, undated (Box 649)
    - map of Piney River Coal Field, undated (Box 649)
    - Sketch map Showing Central West Virginia Sewell Coal Field and rail lines, undated (Box 649)
    - Industrial Map of Wyoming county, West Virginia, undated (Box 649)
    - Map showing land owned & leased by American Collieries co. Snow Hill, West Virginia file no. 6606, undated (Box 649)
    - Map showing land owned & leased by American Collieries co. Snow Hill, West Virginia file no. 6605, undated (Box 649)
    - Penman Mine, Beckley-Fire Creek Coal Co. Property and Sections map. Beckley seam Raleigh County, West Virginia. (Box 649)
  - Prospecting (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 649)
    [Removed from map case drawer entitled "Prospecting".]
    - USGS Topographic Map of Huntersville Quadrangle, West Virginia, 1905 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Summersville Quadrangle, West Virginia, 1915 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Pounding Mill Quadrangle, Virginia-West Virginia, 1916 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Richwood Quadrangle, West Virginia, 1918 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Callaghan Quadrangle, Virginia-West Virginia, 1923 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Dublin Quadrangle, Virginia-West Virginia, 1927 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Warm Springs Quadrangle, Virginia-West Virginia, 1930 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Mountain Grove Quadrangle, Virginia-West Virginia, 1944 (Box 649)
    - USGS Topographic Map of Warm Springs Run Quadrangle, Virginia-West Virginia, 1945 (Box 649)
    - Coal Mines in New River District. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1930/10/08 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-1, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-3, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-2-3, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-3-3, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-4, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-5, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-6, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-1, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-3, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-2-3, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Upper Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-3-3, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-4, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-5, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting: Middle Horsepen Seam map. Bishop, Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc. B-1-6, 1945/11/01 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: Fire Creek seam on the Guyandotte leasehold. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1946/12/28 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map: Tract of Coal land bounded on the North by Lands on the Brule Smokeless Coal Co.; on the West by Still Run Creek; and on the Southwest by Guyandotte Lease of Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1946/12/30 (Box 649)
    - Prospecting Map of No. 6 Seam near Itmann, West Virginia. Pocahontas Fuel Co., Inc., 1947/01/02 (Box 649)